Please stand by for the
123-B test, T-minus-10.
1992 I repeat,
T-minus-10.
Doctor Lorre!
What are you doing?
I need to send a message.
We know too much.
They won't let us go.
I am sending for help.
Everything will be
fine, my little Tweety.
I promise.
You can jump.
Or we can push you.
One day the truth will come out.
Never got on a catapult,
To be flown politely and
reasonably to a destination of your choice
Have you
ever found yourself falling flat
on your face in some violent way?
Have you ever put a huge pile on the road
in the hope of blowing up your arch-enemy?
Have you ever placed TNT and pressed
the fuse, and the fuse itself exploded?
Never open your parachute
Pull the rope and make a pile,
Have any cutlery come out?
It's not your fault.
There's probably someone to blame.
We will be your voice.
Avery.
Jones.
maltese
Justice!
Tuesdays at 14.00
Hey.
Unstoppable force.
I could probably
get you $250 for it.
See you next week.
Thanks for calling
Avery, Jones and Maltese.
If an anvil hits you,
Press 1.
If electrocuted, press 2.
If you've been crushed
by a falling piano, press 3.
Good morning.
It's 3 o'clock.
Wow.
Good morning, Dottie.
Not now.
Do they have
paperwork to support it?
-Hello son
-Did you sleep in a dress?
Good observation.
I was waiting for you.
Hello.
All near the match factories I have
detected fires that have occurred and that
I think there is an opportunity
to help people through a case.
How long was your internship?
There are three more months.
It's enough to dig deep
and make a difference.
You remind me of when I
was fresh out of law school,
and I mean that in a bad way.
I'll take it as a compliment.
No, look.
This is yours..
I will do you a favor
because you are my
nephew and I want
you to live a happy life.
Wait a minute.
I have a feeling
you'll hear this
phrase a lot in Oxford.
At Oxford, they really emphasize
the importance of law in everyday life,
and the only thing you're making me do right
now is brainstorm ideas for your billboards.
Yeah, you're new here, so you
don't know this file goes here.
And that, my friend, is freedom.
I want to buy it.
No, no, no.
I want to file alphabetically.
No, you won't.
Please.
You have a new client
in the conference room.
It looks unstable.
Good luck.
Mr. Coyote?
Coyo..
Coyo happens.
Well, how can I help you?
One of my billboards.
These are quite expensive.
So, did you have an accident?
Don't you speak?
But you have signs.
I don't understand you.
Ok.
Should this be you?
So who is he?
Ok.
It wasn't necessary
to do these, but okay.
Well, I mean... I guess some of you in the past
Trying to
catch a bird that had unpleasant
experiences, backfiring, with that.
.. malfunctioning rocket
Are we talking about skates?
So, uh... Do you have
the rocket skates with you?
OK, great.
We will write your
name as the plaintiff.
And then, well..., We would
like compensation of $300.
$300 Here we
will write the name of the
company that makes the skates.
Let me guess.
Acme.
But little things like this
are great to deal with.
He throws his skates into a box.
We write a complaint and boom!
You will be the richest
jackal in the country.
All I need is a signature.
Or just lick it.
This will probably happen too.
Here we go.
Wait...
Stop, Mr. Jackal!
Hey, someone grab that guy!
Mr. Coyote, look, I just
need you to sign this...
This is an Acme staple.
I guess that's how staples work.
Ok I understand.
There are problems with
Acme's cartoon products.
I see this all the time.
So I was surprised.
My phone and car are
ACME, why would they do this?
No, these are
stupid cartoon things.
What's the worst that could happen?
Do they see birds flying
around their heads?
I don't feel like opening it.
Paige, this is a regular
$300 rocket skate folder.
Trust me.
Doesn't that mean
it's a pile of $300 files?
Paige, come on!
If we present these as evidence,
Do you know what happens?
We have a huge lawsuit ahead of us.
That would be great.
And if you can prove a connection,
then the sky becomes the limit.
The sky's the limit, okay?
The border is right here.
We do not take very large cases.
We'll make it quick
and easy, okay?
Where did all this stuff go?
Mr. Coyote, in my professional opinion,
this bag is worth several hundred dollars;
Also I think the rocket pack
We can also take a look at the change.
That's why you
need to sign this.
Roughly.
Well, it was nice meeting you.
Can you enter the evidence
box into the system?
I'm going to lunch.
Here you go.
Evidence please.
Well, what do we have?
God, someone is
suing for a lot of things.
Excuse me.
Crates of cartoon merchandise
go down to the basement.
NOTIFICATION HAS BEEN MADE
My dear Governor is threatening.
They are equivalent to black men.
The law is completely on our side.
Because we wrote it.
Yes, okay.
It was nice to meet you.
We'd better agree
on the Flappinger case.
Oh, it's over.
Let's say his next vacation will be
in jail, but I have something else.
Cartoon case?
Basement.
I think you should see this.
They're suing us for every
cartoon product from Acme.
Who?
His name doesn't sound familiar.
Pay your debt, or I will sue
you for breach of contract.
OK, I have to go.
I'll call you later, mom.
Okay, okay.
This is not our famous cool guy.
What does this mean?
He's taking on Acme
for cartoon merchandise.
Yes that's true.
Do I look like someone who would take
on the biggest company in the world?
You are looking at the man who
took on the world's largest company.
Channel 4 News,
processing of
legal documents against Acme today.
He just found out that he was placed.
Acme's general counsel Buddy Crane
declined to comment. How did this happen?
It's okay, okay.
Exciting.
All eyes are on you,
You're ready to show it.
Paige, when we sue
Acme for something small,
no one even notices.
We are a small dot on the table.
But this?
This one went to Buddy Crane.
Who?
Buddy Crane.
-The best lawyer in the country.
-Ok.
We went to law school together.
And it is a complete machine.
solid as a rock, his wit is razor sharp;
He cuts his nails with a switchblade.
-I saw him eating lobster once.
-I'll eat too.
But the animal was alive.
I don't think it's legal.
What could I have
done to deserve all this?
Did I anger a witch?
No.
We can.
How did this happen?
I wrote down
everything in the box.
And I brought the box inside.
I was working on my short play.
I've been waiting on the phone for
two hours for tickets to the town fair.
You.
Do you have any idea
what you're doing?
You put me in a
very bad situation.
Hello.
My old friend Kevin.
Yes, it's been a long time.
Look at you,
You're making a mess.
I didn't mix it up
on purpose, actually.
I think we should
talk face to face, right?
Your face and my face?
Be in my office.
Fifteen minutes.
Everything will go smoothly.
OK, so...
From its humble origins,
Acme has become America's
greatest success story.
Acme is an innovation
factory.
We create the impossible.
We revolutionize the industry and
the world with each of our new products.
We value family, We are a
company with family values.
A family of companies.
Acme.
Hey!
I don't know what the deal is, but I
want you to listen to me very carefully.
Stop!
You will follow me.
We'll tell them there
was a misunderstanding.
And we will try to solve
it as soon as possible.
We will be polite.
We will not detonate explosives.
If they put something in
front of us, we will sign it.
Do you understand?
Mr. Avery.
Bill Pelicanos.
And Mr. Coyote.
I'll take you to Buddy.
I heard you are friends, right?
If you were wrong
You could say so.
And look at this guy
choosing clothing optional.
Hello Buddy.
Look who's here?
Yes.
This is Mr. Billboard.
How are you buddy?
Good, good, yes.
Very good.
Those were the days, weren't they?
Yes.
Harvard Law.
You're like...
good.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Ok.
I was a little surprised to see
his name on a case of this size.
Me too.
I mean, I'm so sorry
about all of this.
It was just a big
misunderstanding.
We're having a
really busy day here.
And I'd hate to keep you
from getting back to work...
What are you doing now?
Legal affairs.
Yes.
Yes of course.
My god.
Although it may seem obvious, I must point out that;
ACME denies all accusations.
Mr. Coyote's injuries and life
Among our family products that make it easier
any bond
We declare that there is no.
Yes, yes.
Blah, blah, blah.
Although it's fun to be
in the courtroom with you,
I think it's time to
do what you do best.
-To agree.
-Yes.
Well look, thank you very much.
And I'm so sorry for
taking up your time.
It wasn't intentional.
Oh...
No, no.
He didn't mean it.
Do you have another copy?
Is this a joke?
No no no.
It's not funny at all.
your cartoons are
funny should have been.
Do you want to fight, Avery?
your little company
It has no equal.
We will connect you.
We'll bury it in paperwork.
To ensure that your name
is associated with failure,
I use my best lawyers every day.
I will work on this job 24 hours a day.
Oh, I almost forgot.
We do not cover parking. Do you
know what you could do with $50,000?
Any idea how many birds
you could buy with this?
Lots of them!
It's not really important,
but I'm not there.
Yeah that's right, I quit, man.
Go find another lawyer.
This is already my personal
fucking nightmare and I'm
not going to be there to
see if it can get any worse!
Sorry..
It slipped out of my hand.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why didn't you agree?
We are doing this.
We agreed.
Dottie, what do we do here?
We agree.
Okay, I tried to compromise
but he wouldn't let me.
He's a jackal.
We're not even trial lawyers.
I have a miniature golf
tournament this weekend.
I don't even know if I
can come on Monday.
There is also preparation
for the hearing.
Photocopying in this economy.
If we beat Acme, we
can afford photocopiers.
We can't beat Acme.
I mean, no one has ever
done this and never will.
Even if you quit now,
Acme is on the hook for
legal expenses, attorney
fees, and that's just for now.
So this could close our doors.
Look, if we lose, we lose.
But if we quit, we'll
really lose a lot of money.
Look, we only have one
real goal for this case.
And that's it.
We can't look like fools,
okay?
Our job is not to win this case.
Our job is to still be
involved when it's over.
That's what the soul is.
Let's act like lawyers.
What do lawyers do?
They find evidence and start
making a list of witnesses.
Bird.
He actually won. Every time an Acme
product fails, we become witnesses.
Can confirm Wiley's story.
Sure, whatever.
Witness the Roadrunner
add to our list.
One more thing.
Where will Mr. Coyote stay?
Translation and synchronization into Turkish;
ufukbaba
Okay, don't look at me like that.
Yes, I live in a motel.
It has a pool.
You know, no mortgage.
I don't have to make my bed.
There's an all-you-can-eat
seafood buffet around the corner.
Tissue paper comes out of a
compartment in the bathroom.
Hello Jerry.
Yes?
Wait a second.
Stop it.
Come on.
Well, I need another
room for a few nights.
Don't be near me.
PET
PROHIBITED
Not a pet.
It looks like a pet.
Who rents a separate
room for their pets?
Jerry, come on.
I've been living here
for about five years.
You know me.
No pets.
Ok.
Do you want this?
Legally, a pet is an individual's
comrade, inside or outside his residence,
bred, domesticated or
It is a domesticated animal.
This is Mr.
Coyote.
He is my customer.
In the eyes of the law, it is not my
or anyone else's pet. And therefore,
that sign or any, a rule for him
It's not valid, okay?
It doesn't say there are no animals.
And in my unbiased opinion,
he may sue you
for discrimination.
Yes.
If he pees on the carpet, you pay.
OK, we agreed.
But I need a full
urine analysis.
So this is a motel,
Lots of people pee on the carpet.
Oh, it's right next door.
Certainly.
1 ) GO TO THE CITY
HIRE A LAWYER
SUE ACME
Then a mouse breaks the
sound barrier. Guadalajara.
Albuquerque carrot festival
There's another week to catch up.
Are you having fun?
We are having fun.
You're some kind of
psychopath, aren't you?
TO THE HEARING
15 DAYS
Watch and learn.
Here's how we
receive the subpoena.
It is enough to cover it
with plenty of bird seed.
The Roadrunner takes the bait,
He gets his summons and boom.
He is legally obliged
to come to court.
Roadrunner trap.
Beep, beep.
Is this an issue between you?
Did everyone understand our plan?
No.
Yes.
Paige, what's our plan?
We have to prove to a
jury that Acme products
were at fault for every accident
Wiley has had over the years.
So we'll take photos
and collect evidence.
And we'll put the
evidence in small bags.
We will interview
experts and witnesses.
And we will put forward thick
books of photocopied documents.
We will go to the field and work with all
our strength, and we will study our lesson.
Leaving a kind note in the desert,
our eyewitness We will try to catch it.
And if we follow my plan,
By the end of it, we'll have enough
evidence to bring down Acme.
We really have nothing.
So, I knew we wouldn't have
anything. But this is nothing...
Stand up!
Your Honor Judge Trapa Grosso
presided over by Albuquerque,
The Second Judicial Term
court opened its session.
You can sit.
Person.
Cartoon.
Silence!
My name is Judge Trapa Grosso.
Case name; Coyote vs. ACME.
I am not a lax judge.
I'm a judge who doesn't
do nonsense or stupid things.
Got it?
Excuse me...
Mr. Crane.
Go finish it..
We live in a wonderful
country, don't we?
Because it is a country that
values ​​freedom above all else.
You are free to live
your life as you wish.
It could mean
living in the desert.
In a cave.
I spend my days
more than you, by
chasing after a much
faster, running bird.
But it's your right.
As an American.
But this freedom also means
responsibility It brings with it.
For example, if
we take a missile.
And gluing handlebars to it.
Of course, it's your choice.
But we expect you
to understand this;
That missile and handlebar
were not designed to catch birds.
What I have to prove
to this jury... is that man.
Wile E.
Coyote O...
is careless.
And all of his injuries
were self-inflicted.
So, neither you nor
I will condemn him.
We all know who is responsible.
The desert is clear like the sky..
.
I think just now
I laid an egg.
God bless America.
May God protect our soldiers.
This was really good.
Oh, please don't
write this. And... and..
.
Please don't write this.
Or, or...
him.
Mr. Avery.
Now.
..
So now, what happened.
.. What did he say
we would put forward?
Ha?
So, I know the answer to this.
I know the answer.
I'm not asking you.
I mean, that's a question.
But this is a question I ask myself.
Let me start again.
Objection.
To my beginning..
The defense said we would argue
that the products were dangerous.
And ACNE is being
negligent in selling them.
I really agree with all of this.
I mean,
not fancy but real.
Sheyy.
Pardon.
One, one second, please.
Wait a second...
Wiley, we don't need
proof right now...
Mr. Avery.
Okay, okay.
Excuse me, Your Honor.
My client, I told you that ACME is at fault.
He wants me to show him Rocket Skating.
As you can see, there
is a fault in the switch.
Nothing.
God bless America.
May God protect the soldiers.
Opening statements were made
today in the Coyote v. ACME case.
Sources close to the case report that while Acme
did a great job protecting its brand and reputation,
the plaintiff appeared
hungry and scared.
Then more.
There's still one more week to
catch the Albuquerque carrot festival.
Yes?
241. We receive noise
complaints due to television sound.
Seriously?
So your problem is television.
Okay, I'll close it...
Are you having fun?
We...
Terry, I hung up.
What's up, Doctor?
Who's this?
I can't hear you.
Are you sure it's
the right number?
Your hearing.
Maybe I can come
to ACME and help you.
What?
I have information
that could stop Acme.
Forever.
Oh my God, can
you stop this case?
He has information that will end
everything if he is revealed.
If they figure out what he
knows, he'll be a sitting duck.
So who is this?
Where can I find it?
Write this.
I'll only say it once.
Oh, wait.
I'm taking a pen.
Wait, wait.
666 Terrible Road.
It doesn't seem like
a place I want to go.
Ask about Jack.
ACME has ears everywhere,
It has eyes and ears.
And they're losing people.
Don't forget this.
I don't forget.
Will I be able to
contact you again?
Mr Leghorn.
Buddy, I say buddy,
You little tramp, you.
What was Bora Bora like?
The tax haven is so
beautiful they named it twice.
I heard we have a lawsuit
in the animation industry.
They are doing PR.
you know.
A local newspaper.
And it's quite flattering.
You know I will
win the case quickly.
But in the meantime,
This kind of thing makes us look
pretty good in the eyes of the public.
It's not ideal, but you know, it's
like killing two birds with one stone.
Two birds, one stone?
What a vile statement.
-I just...
-Rotten.
We both know that
Something bigger is going to happen,
and if it did, it would be extremely
unpleasant for everyone involved.
We can't afford to be public.
A mysterious caller.
Very cool.
So what did his voice sound like?
I don't know, it was like, "So,
what's up doctor, I have information."
Bang, bang, bang.
It looked like he was chewing
on crackers or something.
Ok.
The math says it
should be right here.
It's just a wall.
Jack.
Are you a Jack anywhere?
Wait, what's that?
Ah, that's some kind of jack.
Someone has a good sense of humor.
Here is the duck and it is sitting.
It was a little easy.
I like it easy.
Excuse me.
Hello, my name is Kevin Avery.
This is Paige.
I am a personal injury lawyer.
Look who's coming
decided.
Great.
Thank you.
I wasn't sure you
knew we were coming.
You're a little late and you're
still wearing that disgusting outfit.
Take off your pants.
Over here please.
And strike a pose.
Ah.
No.
It is very difficult to find
nude models these days.
Sit down.
Bleach?
We're fine, thank you.
Undress and pretend to think.
I estimate this will
take a few hours.
Oh yes.
We received an anonymous call saying
you may have some important information.
Yes, information that can
help us get into the case quickly.
Information?
Yes.
About ACME?
ACME?
Yes.
ACME.
ACME?
After all this
Do they call me Daffy?
The whole world is Daffy!
ACME ?
AC you.
You can't take it from me!
I will tell you everything.
Your face is covered in ACME!
Everything you need to know
about ACME is inside the box.
Mr. Duck, Mr. Duck!
You shouldn't be here.
I agree, doctor.
Let's destroy this facility...
I'm here for a
no-pants modeling gig.
Look, I'm a horse!
I am a horse!
We drove him crazy and got proof.
It might be important.
He's obviously been
keeping this inside for a while.
Wait.
THIS IS ALL THE NATION This
is all the nation.
Are we a nation?
Do you think we'll be kidnapped?
For ransom?
I feel very alive.
So what do you think?
This seems too dangerous to say.
Still he went in.
What are you doing?
I follow Wiley.
I'll look like a loser
if I stay here now.
I'm coming to the tunnel.
Is there anyone?
I'm sure they don't
tell you to go through
mysterious tunnels in your
fancy lectures at Oxford.
In fact, I bet they
discourage you.
I originally thought of
specializing in mysterious tunnels.
No, you didn't think..
.
Yes, I thought.
What's here?
Hey, I found a message.
What does it say?
Daffy writes.
I'm not sure how
much time I have.
I hope this message reaches you.
Unfortunately, things went wrong...
In The Sisyphus Project.
Sisyphus.
What is the Sisyphus Project?
ACME is watching my every move
and I feel like I'm in grave danger.
If you see this message,
please send help.
Doctor Loree.
Kevin!
Run! Run! Run! Run!
Didn't I say it was too
dangerous to mention?
I said.
-Didn't I say exactly that?
-Yes
What could this mean?
Sisyphus Project?
I... I don't know.
I don't know.
What?
What just happened?
Boss, I think they're after us.
Ok, Sisyphus
It's from ancient Greece.
Every day, a rock is
destroyed by the gods.
He was punished by
being carried to the top.
But it would roll down immediately.
For eternity.
And at the same time That's
what Daffy drew. So what?
This is not proof.
None of this will help the case.
This... this is all
just a waste of time.
I'm sorry, but the warning sign We
have a customer who cannot read.
We have a lot of stuff
that he broke himself.
We have nothing, Paige.
You've been solving ACME cases
for years and you've never stopped.
Stop thinking and see a pattern.
-Is it a pattern?
Yes.
My clients explode and
two seconds later, they're OK.
Nobody cares.
So does that make it normal?
$100?
Is this fair?
This case might fix it.
It's your opportunity to show
people what you can really do.
Yes, but that only
works if I don't lose.
Why do you assume you'll lose?
Are you kidding me?
It's really easy to lose.
And you better learn this.
Everyone thought I was
crazy for coming here.
But I didn't want to go to a
law firm and help them get richer.
Actually still a real I
thought you were a lawyer.
Yes, me too.
So what's up with the Roadrunner?
There are no words.
You know, I really envy you.
You know, it must be nice
to have such a clear goal.
So, I guess I used to have that.
You know, I was
hungry and chasing.
But I didn't like the
pressure to win all the time.
I'm tired of trying.
Anyway, you're a
really good listener.
What are you doing?
Stop!
There is a trap!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
We were talking heart to heart!
Wait!
Wiley!
You can't jump from there!
You did it.
Şeyy, to explain his troubles.
You're making a lot of effort.
Hey, Wiley.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
Are you sitting?
Yes.
But Sal is standing
Is it okay?
Wiley is fooling us.
The only reason he
filed this case is to
capture and kill the
Roadrunner during the trial.
This is not good.
This is all part
of a conspiracy.
He's using us to get the
bird on the witness stand.
If Roadrunner goes to
trial, there will be chaos.
I'll look like a fool.
If the company closes down, we
will become a mattress salesman.
This is a derogatory
term for mattress salesmen
Good morning my baby.
We become garbage collectors.
-Kevin.
-Ok.
Trash people.
My father is a garbage man.
Ok.
Wiley returns to the courtroom
I'm really nervous about it.
There would be no hearing without Wiley.
If there is no hearing, there is no company.
And without the company,
we would be broke.
I don't like to suggest
lying to a dog, but
Roadrunner will be there
You'll have to convince him.
Paige, I was wrong.
With connection to Sisyphus Project
and ACNE See what you can find about it.
Great, I'm already
on top of this.
Ok.
Hello.
I wonder if Dr. Laurie
still lives here?
They're listening, you know.
Would you like some tea, dear?
It was a very happy marriage.
He worked long days but still
came home and talked for hours
He used to play the piano for me
because he knew how much I loved him.
We spent 87 years together.
I am grateful.
Dr. When did Laurie pass away?
If you don't mind me asking?
Oh, he's not dead.
It disappeared.
One day he went to work with our little
bird and I never saw either of them again.
They told me he ran off with
his secretary, but I don't think so.
His secretary was a Penguin.
Tell me about the Sisyphus
Project What can you say?
What?
What day is it?
On what day will
Roadrunner testify?
Any day now.
From where?
Is there a particular reason
you want to catch up with him?
Okay, okay,
I will inform you.
I need this Roadrunner.
Definitely.
Why exactly?
He's the only one who sees every
time this moron misuses our products.
I bet.
He holds a grudge.
Come out and burn with me.
How difficult can it
be to catch a bird?
I'm lying!
Load Bearer Luis!
FREE
Hello.
My husband was the lead inventor
of animated products at ACME.
When you get the job you are very
He was excited.
He wanted to do things that
would really help cartoons.
It's like a de-puffing pump.
Burp lines eraser.
Oh, and this
anti-predator spray.
After a while, things changed.
He didn't like what was happening.
And then he disappeared.
Recently,
I was getting phone calls.
Sometimes they would close it.
But sometimes...
What's up, doctor?
I don't know the person on the phone.
I don't know where my
beloved husband has gone.
But the reason he left I
know it's the Sisyphus Project.
The goal was achieved.
Launch Project Roadkill;
countdown; 3-2-1.
Sir, the target is looking at us.
Why is the target looking at us?
Meep, meep.
Wait!
Wait, wait!
Did we catch him?
I couldn't catch him!
Clearly we hit a speed bump.
Does it itch?
Yes.
But I'm afraid to mention it.
Your eyes and ears were there.
What happened?
What did you see?
I thought, I thought...
Did he teach you to think?
For you to think,
I don't pay money.
-I'm paying for you to talk.
-I taught.
Did you teach? Did you think? Because
you just said, I thought I taught you.
I taught!
What did you teach?
A fault on the eastern ring line.
Ultimately, that's where
the ropes fell apart.
This roadrunner
is very, very fast, sir.
NO!
Step, you gave a sign;
They're getting very close.
I just don't want him to be afraid.
I want him to be destroyed.
I want him to stop tampering.
Dr. You know what
happened to Lorry.
Should the same thing
happen to your grandmother?
NO!
Please!
I'll catch it tonight!
I promise!
Hey, great job, big dog.
Shut up Patches!
Absolutely sir.
Not a word!
Paige?
Are you ok?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
Always from the window
I wanted
to throw a bomb
outside, but I had no luck.
Listen, Dr. Lorry's
widow gave me this tape.
I've listened to it thousands of times.
There is something in the background.
But ACME has ears,
eyes, and ears everywhere.
This is the man who called me.
Yes I know but can you hear it?
I wish I could say more.
But ACME has ears,
eyes, and ears everywhere.
Wait, wait..
That's the proof.
OK, that's enough.
Wiley.
Wiley!
Stop it.
Is there some kind of plan for this?
CHANGE
Here it is.
Wait, I know this song.
From where?
Like a TV show
or commercial or...
Wait.
Albuquerque Carrot Festival.
OK, what is this?
Carrot festival in Albuquerque.
It happens every year.
Is there anyone?
Mysterious person?
Mysterious person calling me?
Avery, Jones, Maltese too.
Avery, Jones.
We come from Maltese.
You can show yourself
whenever you want.
So what's up, Doctor?
Who is there?
I'll never tell you, Mac.
I am a creature of the
night, I am a moving shadow.
You'll never understand who I am.
My god.
Dear God.
You saw my face.
Don't look at me.
I'm so... beautiful.
Mysterious Caller?
Let me put it this way;
That lovebird
has been tripping over your
side of this case for weeks.
You're lucky to
have me by your side.
Hey, have you been followed?
Eyes on you? Have you
been caught on Mobese?
Did he see the drone?
Did they listen?
This is getting
embarrassing now.
Look, I have a million
questions for you.
Why didn't you call again?
Dr.
What happened to Lauree?
What can you tell us
about the Sisphus Project?
That's enough questions, lawyer.
This needs a response.
As you can see, Dr. Laurie was the
chief inventor of ACME cartoon products.
He built great things.
quick change machine,
basic needs such as.
One day they sent a manager from
the company to inspect the work.
The man was a real toy.
Suddenly many secrets were revealed.
They called it the
Sisyphus Project.
Testing has become more reckless
under the new administration.
I'm not sure I understand.
What was all this for?
They weren't inventing
products for cartoons.
They were using cartoons
to invent products.
Dr. Lauree says this
is wrong and, cartoon
characters
He said it caused damage.
He begged them
to put an end to this.
But instead they
put an end to it.
Worked on the Sisyphus Project
Everyone who is is either lost,
He was either forced to work
for ACME or he is a charlatan.
So when did the program end?
Don't you see?
It's never over.
It has evolved.
Instead of testing dangerous
products in a laboratory,
they release them
into the real world.
Yes.
Wiley's rocket skates
were designed for recoil.
Now you understand.
The more something breaks, the
more damage the cartoon character gets.
More data to build better
ACME products for people.
Absolutely, absolutely.
Wiley, you are what they
call a high usage user.
They let you explode
and create havoc for years.
In court this
Will you testify?
The world needs to hear this.
No, no. You need someone from
the inside to tell you the truth.
Have ACME's public
relations officer testify.
He is a master of perception management.
Its name is...
Ooo ooo...
It's my turn.
I think they caught him.
No.
If anyone asks, tell them your informant
is a little hunter with a funny hat.
We trust you.
Goodbye.
SECURITY SYSTEM
Great.
No one will pass
through that door.
Any added security is great.
Can you tell us about
your role at ACME?
Slow...Slow...
OK, great.
-If he says something wrong, take him out.
-Ok.
What does your job as a public
relations representative entail?
Everything is very easy.
So you are authorized to
speak on behalf of ACME.
What can you tell us
about the Sisyphus Project?
Mr. Satan, What is
the Sisyphus Project?
I remind you that you are under oath.
I object.
Lawyers, approach the podium.
This case is turning my
courtroom into a circus.
They just threw out my witness.
We don't know this.
I couldn't agree more.
The prosecution's evidence... I request
that he be excluded from the case.
Keep the original pair of rocket skates
Others are overdoing it.
The proposal was accepted.
Are you kidding?
Your Honor. Due to lack of evidence I
am requesting dismissal because of this.
The proposal was accepted.
I'm tired of all this nonsense.
You don't say that.
That's the beauty of being dominant.
I can say whatever I want.
Invalid trial?
There I said it.
The case was dismissed.
What happened there was a miscarriage
of justice, but it was not a surprise.
For decades, ACME
has knowingly produced
dangerous products in cartoon characters.
He gives it
to his hand.
ACME, "The Sisyphus Project" to cover up an insidious
conspiracy called He made great efforts to do so.
They threatened my
and my client's safety.
Look, bombs, rocks, pianos,
They will not give up anything.
But me and my partners
will continue the fight.
So these companies think they can do whatever
they want and get away with anything.
Because they are getting away with it.
But we're tired of it.
And now it will be over. That's
why we're preparing for a launch..
.
Excuse me, just a minute.
Wiley!
There was more chaos in court
today after the ACME case was
dismissed by the very fair and
respected Judge Tropo Grosso.
The plaintiffs voiced their objections with a
cartoonish rocket approximately six feet tall.
Everything is fine.
There's nothing to see here.
Is this your car?
Hello Paige.
Have you seen?
What?
Your speech.
It's the country's number
one trending news right now.
Everywhere.
What?
Did they like my speech?
And I think the car
boom is part of it.
Mr. Avery.
Mr.
Avery.
I need to close it.
Mr. Avery. Mr. Avery. Do you have any
comments about Congress accepting your case?
Congress?
Your thoughts on Foghorn
Leghorn's testimony.
Now... Did you say Congress?
They study ACME.
You're going to DC.
Are we going to DC?
We're going to DC.
OK, no comments.
Mr. Avery.
Mr.
Avery. Thanks a lot.
Where are you going?
CAVE What?
No! You can't go.
I need you in D.C.
So, this is the big showdown.
If you don't show up,
there won't be a hearing.
All this would be in vain.
Roadrunner will be there.
Yes, of course.
It will be there.
Yes it is coming.
I promise.
Come on.
What are you saying?
The whole world will watch.
It will be there.
Ok.
Come on.
Let's go.
Initially seems like a
routine product failure
The apparent situation is as old as time
It turned into a David-Goliath fight.
To our furry little friend
We wish you good luck in D.C.
We support you, Wiley.
And we always were.
From day one.
When a company is this successful,
There will be people who want to destroy it.
But our hands are clean.
Flight attendants, prepare for landing.
What we did when leaving Albuquerque
Sorry for the wrong turn, folks.
This is it.
No more.
I don't care if you kidnap him, run him
out of town, or throw him in a ditch.
Wiley Coyote will not be
at the hearing tomorrow.
Got it?
Yes boss.
We will clean it.
Please be quiet.
Wiley, please be quiet.
Look, rest assured, the things I have to
do are much more important than yours.
There's been a change in plans.
FROM WHERE?
WHAT HAS CHANGED?
Look, he...
He failed.
Is it ok?
Why Isn't He Coming?
FROM WHERE?
Okay, okay.
Do you think I'm going to
drag the Roadrunner here
so you can destroy me in
front of the whole world?
Yes, I want him to be in court
so we can catch him and eat him.
I know you want it. Why
should I help you do this?
OK, yes.
I lied.
I needed you to stay on this case.
But do you know?
You lied to me too.
You misled me.
You made me think this
case was about something.
And so it is.
You know, it's much
bigger than the Roadrunner.
You didn't even understand
what the rabbit said, did you?
You are a high usage user.
I mean, look at these.
You are addicted.
Every explosion.
Don't fall into the bottom
of the canyon one at a time.
ACME wanted this.
You know, I changed
my whole life for you.
My entire routine.
You'll probably all explode at me,
because you wanted a baguette.
Oh, me?
All this time you only
cared about your own plan.
Oh, Roadrunner. roadrunner
I'm so sick of this Roadrunner.
You'll never catch him!
Is it ok?
You just...
You can't really catch it...
Stop trying.
-Yes.
-Hello Kev.
Look, I didn't want to tell you
this right before the hearing.
But...
We spent our last
penny on this case.
We ran out of money.
So what does this mean?
That means, unless there's
some kind of miracle,
There is no
company to return to.
I've made an appointment
for plasma donation next week.
I can't go.
I don't want to put that
kind of pressure on you.
We thought you should know.
Ok.
You missed it!
Wiley!
Oh boy.
I'm trying to save you!
I
Ah!
Ah,
What is waiting?
He's in the bathroom.
Looks like you had a rough night.
Ha?
Thank you for your convincing interest.
Come on.
Do you really want to go there?
So...
We will see about this.
There are cameras.
Pressure.
What's this?
This is everything you've ever wanted.
Freedom from responsibility.
This is not subject to any conditions.
So under the table.
This is for you.
All I have to do now
is walk out this door.
Come on.
I really want to keep doing the
same thing over and over again.
Try, fail,
try, fail.
We expect a different result.
I just realized this...
Yes.
You get the gist.
My god.
You look like a stuntman.
Is Wiley here?
Isn't he with you?
I haven't seen him since we were driving
80 miles per hour on the highway,
hooked up to the refrigerator.
What the hell?
I thought you were in
the hotel room next to me.
I feel so left out.
I really screwed up.
He knows the Roadrunner won't come.
He knows I'm lying.
Ah.
I'm an idiot.
I had to be honest with him.
It seemed easier.
Mr. Avery, thank you
for joining us today.
We're here to decide whether it is or not.
ACME products pose a danger to society.
Where was your customer?
To be honest, I'm
not exactly sure.
Senator Fudd, Mr. Coyote's
presence at the scheduled time.
that he did not find it
necessary to honor us
It will tell you everything you
need to know about his character.
Hmm.
I think this tells us a lot.
Look, my client has
a long history. ACME.
He has been using his
products for decades.
If so, why...
Dangewus?
Actually he has no other choice.
ACME has a monopoly on all the tools
necessary for Mr. Coyote's business.
Is it his job?
Here I learned that he was
unemployed and living in a cave.
Hahaha.
This is true.
This is a fact.
TRUE.
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
According to Sylvester V. Chasing predators is
a legal profession under the law, Gonzales said.
Maybe he doesn't get
a salary, but he works.
In fact, he is one of the hardest
working people I have ever met.
And he is brave.
He will walk on the smallest
tightrope over the largest canyon.
It will ride on a rocket to
which it is manually locked.
It will hit the handlebars too.
Without blinking an eye.
So.
..
Oh.
Ah.
I am sad.
To look.
When Mr.
Coyote first walked
into my office,
I was the laziest person
you could imagine.
I didn't want to work.
I didn't want to try anything.
Because deep down
I didn't want to fail.
But he is not afraid of it.
No matter what, he
pulls himself together.
He tries again and
again and again.
He would never think of giving up.
He wakes up every morning
with purpose and hope.
And I think everyone
should be inspired by this.
I know I am.
You don't need signs anymore.
Thank you for coming back.
Mr. Leghorn, thank you for taking
time out of your busy schedule.
We asked Mr. Avery to ask
you a few questions today.
I was researching
this guy in interviews.
He is a braggart.
He has a very big ego.
Here I am, son.
Certainly.
I can work with this.
Mr. Leghorn, are you aware of the
ACME program known as Project Sisyphus?
I am.
I'm familiar with your name.
Ok.
So how do you explain the type
of program to this committee?
Actually, this is a matter of
research and development.
Great.
So are you constantly innovating your
cartoon product line to make it better?
Yes son.
Ok.
This makes sense.
So if you examine
these products so
closely, why do
they fail so often?
This looks like something
you could tinker with.
Boy, things are complicated.
Ok.
So, is any of the
information you received from
the Sisyphus Project used
to improve the human race?
Certainly.
Ok.
So you confess.
He just confessed.
Have you heard of this?
He admitted it.
Are you knowingly giving
dangerous products to cartoons, and
are you deliberately causing
pain to millions in the process?
Think progress isn't
worth a little pain?
Some discomfort?
That's right, son.
It always was.
And nothing we do
today or any day is illegal.
Isn't that right, Mr. Crane?
Definitely.
The law is completely
on our side here,
and so is the opinion
of the silent majority.
Thank you, Mr. Crane.
Mr Leghorn.
And something else.
Sit down son.
I'm asking the questions here.
There is nothing sweeter
than this prosecutor.
I remembered my days as a
little rooster on the poultry farm,
where I learned
a valuable lesson.
Cartoons are resilient.
Hit us with a hammer.
Throw us off the cliff.
We can have it.
Cartoon-speaking, I think it
might even be a little funny.
Am I right?
So, what's a little pain
for the greater good?
Pain is a part of
life and it is valuable.
You like that comfortable elastic
in those shoes, don't you son?
This is duty free.
We developed it by bouncing
it off a cartoon a million times.
These hurricane pills
turned into jet propellers.
This high-speed tonic
took us to the moon.
So yes, our cartoon
products sometimes explode.
Sometimes they backfire.
Sometimes they push the
limits of gravity and science.
But do you all want to live in
a world where there is no new?
Without progress?
Now, what is it that you
always say? Mr. Crane?
You can't make an omelette without it.
I break some eggs.
Yes, that's true.
And in this case, if this egg,
If he is a despicable desert dog with no connections,
no family, no friends, living in
a cave, I'm sorry, but so be it.
No harm, no foul.
This is not an accurate
portrayal of my client.
No one should act on his
behalf except his lawyer.
I was under the
impression he wouldn't talk.
Does anyone in the whole world
care what happens to the coyote?
Mr. Runner, we will ask you a
series of yes or no questions.
Two beeps for
yes, A beep for no.
Do you understand?
Beep, beep.
Are you a bird?
Are you easy to catch?
Beep.
OK, nice.
Do you know Mr. Wile E.?
Jackal?
Beep, beep.
Have you witnessed
Mr. Does Coyote use any
acne products while he's
with you in the desert?
Beep, beep.
Have these products always failed?
Mr. Runner, were you Mr. Runner's
witness? Coyote's pain and suffering?
Yes, me too.
Can you call him my friend?
Thank you, Mr.
Runner.
Thank you for coming here today. Is there
anything you would like to say additionally?
Okay, the place is yours
to add to the record.
Will you come back?
Mr. Avery, I must
admit that I am very...
very
touched.
However, you have provided no evidence of ACME's culpability
other than the pain and suffering of this unique coyote.
Therefore, no matter how much it
pains me, you leave me no choice.
Everyone agrees to reject
this investigation, say yes.
Yes.
Yes!
Try… fail.
Okay, no hard feelings, guys.
It's a tough world out there.
Better luck next time.
I think these are the
birds you are looking for.
Let me see you.
Offensively ridiculous!
What's in automation?
Get me out of here!
I want justice!
If someone is my friend...
We tried.
Thank you both for pushing me.
To wait.
What's going on?
Look!
These are lawyers!
They are here!
I can't believe it!
Thank you for what you
do behind the scenes.
What's this?
They all want to sue ACME.
Even after you helped...
Unfortunately you did.
They trust you.
Avery Jones and Malta.
Hey!
Can you believe this?
Not being able to!
It looks like you have something
very important in your office.
We understand.
Hello, Counselor.
You fought a good
fight in the congress.
But nothing proves the guilty
better than cold, hard evidence.
Here is a gift from you, truly,
through the doors of ACME.
What's this?
There are approximately
five years of lawsuits.
It's like we have our
work cut out for us.
A shocking new development in
the operation. Today is the ACME case.
Newly leaked footage from Project
Sisyphus triggered a pre-dawn raid on the
company's headquarters, prompting ACME
general counsel and CEO Foghorn Leghorn Buddy
It led to Crane's swift arrest for
their involvement in the alleged abuse.
I am an uncaged rooster!
Additionally, investigators at the scene
reported that investigators had identified Dr.
ACME scientist Peter Lorre
disappeared 30 years ago.
His upcoming testimony about the
Sisyphus Project promises
to bring the truth to light.
Oh dear!
Well, don't be a stranger.
The sky is the limit.